LINDSEY DUBNICKA

Milwaukee, WI | 507-219-7479 | lindseymiller2567@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/lindseydubnicka | GitHub: https://github.com/lindseymiller2567

Portfolio: https://lindseymiller2567.github.io/react-portfolio

PROFILE

Front-end Web Developer with a background in the graphic arts, and newly developed skills in JavaScript, CSS, responsive web design, and React. Earned a certificate in full stack web development from the University of Wisconsin.

Successfully collaborated with a development team to create an interactive web application that lets users explore new recipe ideas for planning a dinner party. With each project, I strive to create a meaningful web experience for the end-user while also writing clean and organized code that follows ES6 best practices. Known as a detail-oriented and tech-savvy professional with a strategic vision to harness team creativity and work toward innovating solutions.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks & Libraries: Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Mongoose, Sequelize

Other: Restful APIs, Node.is, MongoDB, MySQL, GitHub, GraphQL, Apollo server, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe

Illustrator, Microsoft Office

PROJECTS

Bookworm

GitHub: https://github.com/Hmlessard/Bookworm | Deployed: https://asgardians-bookworm.herokuapp.com

- Blog-style web application for booklover's to come together to share thoughts and discuss their favorite books. Requires users to log-in or sign up to participate in discussions.
- Collaborated with a team of three to create a web app using MVC architecture pattern. Responsible for setting up the models, creating some of the API routes, and styling the page.
- Technologies Used: Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Handlebars.js, Bcrypt, session storage, Book
 Cover Web API, JavaScript, Bootstrap

Dinner Party Planner

GitHub: https://github.com/MattKolbach/DinnerPlanner | Deployed: https://mattkolbach.github.io/DinnerPlanner

- Client-side web application that lets users search through dinner and drink recipes to help them prepare the perfect spread for an upcoming dinner party.
- Joined forces with a team of three other developers to create a web app using third party API's. In charge of the overall UI and implementing the Pure CSS Library. Contributed to the feature that allows users to save their favorite recipes.
- Technologies Used: JavaScript, Pure CSS, TheCocktailDB Web API, TheMealDB Web API, local storage

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Catalog Print Project Coordinator

Arandell Corporation | Menomonee Falls, WI | July 2019 - Present

- Oversee catalog print projects throughout the manufacturing process while managing client relationships.
- Work with internal departments to help those involved gain alignment on client's needs and requirements.
- Contribute to the company's internal software development by testing new software features, and participating in workflow improvement meetings.
- Conceptualized and helped develop a job tracker that keeps track of all major milestones, tasks and due dates of a project throughout the project's lifecycle.
- Enhance the department's training program while participating on a team that creates best practice documents.

Packaging Graphics Project Coordinator

Schawk | Minneapolis, MN | December 2015 - September 2018

- Managed and coordinated anywhere from 30–80+ projects simultaneously in a fast-paced environment, paying attention to all details to ensure each project's success.
- Built relationships with and maintained direct contact for clients, internal departments and vendors on current projects to ensure alignment of goals, process and expected results.
- Directed packaging artwork fulfillment processes from initial concept and design through pre-press for various international brands.
- Ensured all brand standards were met throughout design and production art stages to ensure the delivery of a superior product.
- Created project timelines and ensured deadlines were met by coordinating with key project stakeholders, including designers, production artists, scheduling managers and clients. Utilized creative problem solving collaboration meetings to overcome roadblocks and detours that could have put the project at risk for on-time delivery of a quality product.
- Reviewed and evaluated electronic graphic art and supporting files, such as fonts, images, and vector files, for print readiness.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate | UW-Extended Campus Coding Boot Camp November 2021 - May 2022

Graphic Communications Management, Bachelors | UW-Stout | Menomonie, WI September 2011 - June 2015